Guide to the Francis C. Moon papers, 1961-2009.
Moon, Francis C. papers
- Series XII. Magnetic Fusion Superconducting Magnet Design Reports
  - Tokamak Experimental Power Reactor Studies, June, 1975 (Box 10)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: CTR Program, Argonne National Laboratory
  - PDX Toroidal Field Coils Stress Analysis, January, 1976 (Box 10)
    Author: Nikodem, Z.D. and R.A. Smith
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Plasma Physics Laboratory, Princeton University
  - PPPL S-I Spheromak Project, Engineering Handbook, November, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Wisconsin Superconductive Energy Storage Project, Volume 1, July 1, 1974 (Box 10)
    Author: Ballou, J.K., et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Engineering Experiment Station, College of Engineering, University of Wisconsin, Madison.
  - Noncircular Tokamak Power Reactor Design, Volume 1, July, 1976 (Box 11)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Electric Power Research Institute, University of Wisconsin, Madison
  - Noncircular Tokamak Power Reactor Design, Volume 2, July, 1976 (Box 11)
  - EPR-Fusion Conceptual Design, Volume 1, December, 1976 (Box 11)
    Author: Baker, C.C.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Electric Power Research Institute, General Atomic Company
  - EPR-Fusion Conceptual Design, Volume 2, December, 1976 (Box 11)
  - EPR-Fusion Conceptual Design, Volume 3, December, 1976 (Box 11)
  - EPR-Fusion Conceptual Design, Volume 4, December, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Fusion Power: Status and Options, June, 1977 (Box 11)
    Author: Gough, William G.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Electric Power Research Institute, McDonell Douglas Astronautics Company
  - Fusion Applications of Homopolar Machines, January, 1978 (Box 11)
    Author: Thomassen, Keith I.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Electric Power Research Institute, University of California, Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory
  - Safety Considerations of Tokamak Fusion Power Reactors, July, 1978 (Box 11)
    Author: Kastenberg, William E., David Okrent
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Electric Power Research Institute, University of California, Los Angeles
  - Definition and Conceptual Design of a Small Fusion Reactor, April, 1979 (Box 11)
    Author: Carlson, G.A., et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Electric Power Research Institute, Lawrence Livermore Laboratories, General Atomic Company, and Pacific Gas and Electric Company
  - Fusion EPR Design Tasks, February, 1980 (Box 11)
    Author: Prater, R., et al.
  - Field Reversed Mirror Pilot Reactor, September, 1980 (Box 11)
  - GA TNS Project, Volume V, Reactor Engineering and Design, October, 1978 (Box 11)
    Author: Project Staff
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: General Atomic Company
  - Isabelle Superconducting Magnets, Preliminary Review, December, 1980 (Box 11)
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Magnet Technology Group, Francis Bitter National Magnet Laboratory, Massachusetts Institute of Technology
  - Status of the Tokamak Program, July 24, 1981 (Box 11)
    Author: Sheffield, John
  - Ormak F/BX, A Tokamak Fusion Test Reactor, June, 1974 (Box 11)
    Author: Haubenreich, P.N., M. Roberts
  - Design Study of Superconducting Magnets for a Combustion Magnetohydrodynamic Generator, March, 1977 (Box 11)
    Author: Thome, Richard J. and John W. Ayers
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Magnetic Corporation of America
  - The Moving-Ring Field-Reversed Mirror Reactor Annual Report Executive Summary, 1979-1980 (Box 11)
    Author: Smith, A.C., et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Pacific Gas and Electric Company
  - Preliminary Design of a Tandem-Mirror-Next-Step Facility, December 18, 1980 (Box 11)
    Author: Damm, C.C., et al.
    Publisher/Distributor/Presented to/Prepared For: Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory
  - Tandem Mirror Fusion Test Facility MFTF-B, Conceptual Design Report and Project Proposal, January 23, 1980 (Box 11)
    Author: Thomassen, Keith I., V.N. Karpenko